dynamicsearch.com.au 2015-04-02

# » Privacy Policy - Australian Local Business Directory

**Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy identifies and describes the way Dynamic Search uses and protects the information we collect about Customers, Users and Visitors. All Customers, Users and Visitors are subject to this Privacy Policy.

**Privacy Commitments**

Dynamic Search takes your privacy very seriously. Our customers told us they want to see clear, easy-to-read information about our privacy commitments and policy.

We have made our privacy policy easier to find and easier to read. And we’re listening.

Our privacy commitments are fundamental to the way we do business every day. These apply to everyone who has a relationship with Dynamic Search — including customers and site visitors.

  * We will protect your privacy and keep your personal information safe. We use powerful encryption and other security safeguards to protect customer data, including your credit cards information which we may store.

  * We will not sell your personal information to anyone, for any purpose.

  * Our customers are in control and you can change, delete or cancel your listing at anytime.

You can send us questions or feedback on our privacy policy by emailing [legal@dynamicsearch.com.au](mailto:legal@dynamicsearch.com.au)

**The Information We Collect, How We Collect It, And How We Use It**

We collect different types of personal, public and other information based on your use of our products and services and our business relationship with you.

Some examples include:

  * Contact Information that allows us to communicate with you, including your name, address, telephone and fax number, e-mail address and website as well as general business information;
  * Billing information related to your financial relationship with us — including your payment data, credit history, credit card number, security codes, and service history;

We collect information in three primary ways:

  * You give it to us when you interact with us about a product or service we offer or provide;
  * We collect it automatically when you visit our Web sites or use our products and services;
  * Third party’s may provide us with general information about your business or through publicly available information on the internet, and collected automatically by the Dynamic Search crawler.

We use the information we collect in a variety of ways, including to:

  * Provide you with the best customer experience possible;

  * Provide the services you purchase, and to respond to your questions;
  * Communicate with you regarding service updates, offers, and promotions;
  * Deliver customised content and advertising that may be of interest to you;
  * Display non-confidential information like business name, contact information and company industry and description on Dynamic Search for public directory assistance purposes.
  * Address network integrity and security issues;

For us to provide you with our service, we must have the ability to properly communicate with you via email or in writing. It is therefore part of the term and conditions of our agreement of use of this site. If you do not want to receive communication from our company, you must remove and delete your listing immediately, see instructions for removing your listing below.

**Third Party Websites**

Dynamic Search may promote third party websites which are not entities, related or in the control of our company. We do not endorse third party websites and you should review and understand the terms and conditions of these websites before using their services and or providing them with any business or personal information.

**Third Party Communication**

If you provide an email address when creating your business listing or when you updating your business listing, your email address will not be shown publically. By providing your email address, users of the site will have the ability to email you via our site. If you prefer not to receive emails from users of the site, please remove your customer contact email address from our site.

**Business Listings Created By A Third Party (users)**

The basis of the Dynamic Search website is to provide a platform for users to promote their business. We are unable to verify the authenticity of the user when creating the business listing. If you find a business listed which is either false, inaccurate or misleading, please immediately contact [legal@dynamicsearch.com.au](mailto:legal@dynamicsearch.com.au) noting the business listing name and your concern. We will endeavour to investigate the matter as soon as possible.

**Removing Your Business Listing**

If you decide to change, delete or cancel your listing at anytime, you can either delete yourself by logging in and manually updating, or by contacting us direct via email and request us to delete on your behalf, if you contact us direct, you must provide us with your company name as displayed on our website. legal@dynamicsearch.com.au

**Maintenance, Updates And Site Changes**

Our mission is to build Australia’s leading business directory. To enable this we must continue to introduce new facilities, services and features to the website. We also reserve the right to change these features without notice including updating this Privacy Policy. We recommend Customers, Users and Visitors review the terms and conditions and this privacy policy each time when accessing and using the site.
